So you want these prisoners brought back?
No.
I want them put in the earth.
I doubt they'll give you any choice.
They had their chance with the Sun King's generosity.
So now they face mine a bounty on all their heads.
If I did this for you, I need a lead on them.
Roz Grand.
We pulled out of a crack in dust Mesa, where he'd been tinkering with his bombs and given will be trying to pay his way across the lake.
I burned my palm on it.
Looking bright Market.
You never know when I might need these
down.
Yeah,
yeah.
Get it over with.
Damn.
Yeah.
Party, little plant.
You'll help.
Yeah.
What?
Her hands?
Yeah,
Keep it for later.
Here.
Wait.
Got their attention.
Really?
Here.
Here we go again.
No.
Oh, there.
I thought they send soldiers.
Mighty card.
Empire must be more strapped than I thought.
Oh said
no matter.
Bounty hunters die like the rest.
Welcome to my ravine of death.
Are you serious?
Safest murderer Trap.
Make all these things.
That's why they put me in that stinking hole.
I'm curious.
I don't suppose those behemoths a call to the President killed John.
Eva, You're gonna be disappointed.
Yeah.
That's why I have my toys to distract me from the pain.
Yes.
Oh, you're a trickster.
Careful now.
No slave.
Not yet.
Little acrobat.
What?
Yeah,
but you're not on fire yet.
Persistent.
Aren't you
okay?
Yeah.
You got me.
No more tramps.
Tell your neighbour I'll be a good boy from now on.
You expect me to believe that?
What's in your hand?
Oh, this just a little.
I guess he died doing what he loved.
There's
no way
stocking up
and
okay.
Yeah.
And
you,
You
you
no turning back.
What?
Morning.
You don't talk that a way.
We could
you
some kind of figurine?
I think it's the nuke.
Freeze!
Fellow back!
Weakness to fire.
Strong against Freeze!
Freeze!
Canister Galit destroying this component disables arranged.
Freeze Attack!
Cargo sack.
Destroying this component disables arranged elemental attack and triggers an explosion.
Yeah,
Sun's headed.
Okay.
I can't get out of this.
The Sun King owes his life to an Outlander.
Strange
two.
If this given came through here.
Seems like a good place to start asking
as the sun is my witness.
I never had a Nora in my house.
What about a man named Yvonne?
No.
Can't say I've heard that name, but we're a trading town.
Get a lot of people through all kinds, I'm sure, like ones who don't want to be followed.
I never heard of You're given if he's trouble.
Well, I can't say I'm sorry.
Now I thinks to be doing nor a girl, if you don't mind.
He was suspicious at all
time to take a look around.
How did he get so close to the Sun King?
The officer on guard will be blaming their shadows from mistakes.
You wouldn't have gone
make for the harbour.
And you didn't go.
Said it given Find his friends, his enemies.
I suppose they're all the same to me.
Looks like I'm happy to see him.
Don't you pass out.
Give on.
I'm not done with you.
If you can break out of Sunstone Rock, you can take a bit of knife play, can't you?
You didn't break out.
You're a snitch.
Come to bring Meridian down on us.
This is my operation now, so I have to make a show of you.
Hey!
Get shot!
So they woke up.
They sent you to take me back to Sun Stone not to take you back.
Uh well has she has done your job for you?
Geneva said you were a smuggler.
Only for the shards.
Is that true?
I could tell you anything.
A sick mother or I did it for the poor Children.
Would he be lying in the year I spent in a cage?
All I regret, it was killing that guard because it got me caught.
You can take that back to Sunstone Rock.
No,
no,
Some kind of figurine.
I think it's been nuke.
There is much I would confess to you.
But one thing I cannot I did not kill Signature our chieftain who claimed to be your father that night I was alone in my tent drunk with cold wine, dreaming as I always did, Billy, your mother in her sunset smile You will never hear my testament And my offering will never touch the warmth of your hands.
But I paint my mark in the light of truth.
I know what I am guilty of and what I am not.
I hope against hope that in your heart you know the same
rumours of the north by the well travelled
readers.
Many times I have been asked to describe that most fearsome of barbarian tribes, the nor of the Savage East.
So ferocious are the rumours of these people.
You might think it was they who raided us during the dark times of the Madsen King and not the opposite.
Well, dear readers, though I possess bravery.
There is a shadow length between bravery and certain death, and it is certain death awaits any who trespass on the sacred land of the Nora.
However, I have travelled beyond date our into the snow dusted hinterlands of the savage east and on to the very edge of your territory.
Now, the site of a hardscrabble trading camp known as hunters gathering there sat around and opened fire Without Landers and un coup THS, I was able to gather tales and eyewitness accounts of what might be seen within the Valley of the Warrior women.
They told me another day's travel South lies the mother's crown, a name that suggests something grander than the Ford of tree trunks and log cabins that was described to me.
Still, I was assured it squats most imposingly upon a rocky outcrop far above rushing rapids and white capped falls from its ramparts of Syriza's Watchtower stretch back across the mountains.
And at any sign of approach, flaming arrows arc into the air between them or a tribe so concerned with their precious wilds.
I expected less careless behaviour.
Those interlopers, stat or foolhardy enough to approach after this display or turned back with another flight of arrows this time aim just above their heads.
The outlanders chuckle ing agreed that if a car just showed their colours, thie arrows would fly lower and that even soldiers behind a towers.
Wallace grumble about being ambushed and devoured by Nora Warriors.
I corrected them that it was the tenor, not the Nora, who are known to engage in cannibalism.
In fact, the nor have only been seen to to the bark from trees, the tough plants from the ground and drink strange, durable bruise.
I proposed that they may well be forbidden from eating meat, except that they're strange feminine rights beneath the moon.
Yes, in the benighted land of the Nora, the natural way of things goes inverted.
Women rule men and all the might of card a metal can be deflected by logs, leather and hides.
Ruins filled with bounteous artefacts go untouched, and great stretches of farmable land are left uncultivated.
Only the machines, which the North greatly mistrust after some ancestral conflict or another c'mon, troubled by this rampant strangeness, Father Son has no place here, and I would not be surprised to find the Nora's woman got to be the moon itself, though it is, nor women who so famously feature in tales of encounters with the tribe.
Men have also been sighted, bearing the outlandish hair and blue painted markings of Nora warriors.
It is my understanding from reading older studies of the tribe that a ritual known as the proving allows men to battle one another to gain favour from their rulers.
My curiosity to witness this and other nor a ritual sadly goes on stated.
But it is my hope that his luminous will extend an offer of alliance to these mysterious barbarians.
So emboldened by the Sun King's generosity and the knowledge that I would travel with many, many well armoured laizans, I would gladly gather a firsthand account for the benefit of my readers.
Indeed, I plan to employ a female scribe who might allow better parley between the Nora and I on such an occasion, a better path for a young Kharja woman and working as a seller for the saucer and metal merchants in town.
Know, until such a son touch.
Time comes, though, I can only share with you copies from the extensive collection of sketches I have gathered over the years, mere glimpses of these bizarre, savage and yet still strangely alluring women folk.